Our total budget came
out to 950 million gil.
Our chances of winning are about 70%.
If it's all right with you, there
are more avenues I can explore...
Nah.
You've already done so much.
Thank you.
It was noth—
Hey, Krai!
If you don't end up winning, I'll just
steal it from that aristocrat brat for you.
Liz!
Doing something like that would
just put Krai under suspicion!
You'll have to make it look like some
violent bandits or something...
Let's end the joke there, shall we?
The Reversible Face...
I definitely want it, but...
Let go!
I don't want any more trouble...
You let go first!
If I don't win it at today's
auction, I'll just give up.
If I accrue more debt,
Eva will get really mad again.
Let This Grieving Soul Retire!
Let This Grieving Soul Retire
Yup!
"I Want to Win the Bid No Matter What!"
Episode 13
I Want to Win the Bid No Matter What
Wow!
So many people!
Are they all here to take
part in the auction?
A lot of spectators, too.
Good morning, Master!
Wait, you guys came, too?
You've become friends, huh?
Oh, no. I just came to see
your magnificent self.
Then I randomly ran into them.
Long time no see, Krai.
Nice to see you both!
Hi, Rhuda.
So I've heard...
Heya.
Hello, Tino.
there's some incredible relic
you're trying to get your hands on.
Sounds like your debt's
through the roof, too!
Yeah, something like that.
But, Tino... How come you came by yourself?
You could've come with us.
Well...
I didn't get invited.
Sorry, I completely forgot.
W-Well, I've been attracting
a lot of unwelcome attention lately.
You probably shouldn't be around me.
That's Thousand Tricks.
Yup, yup!
I heard the relic is incredible.
All-powerful, I heard.
More attention than I even imagined.
That's it!
Tino, how would you like to be
my agent at the auction?
Your... agent?
Right.
When I give you the signal,
you raise the paddle and bid.
13.27 million gil!
It's a rare opportunity,
so why don't you all enjoy yourselves, too?
Are you sure?
Sure.
I've done it tons of times already.
Aw, but I wanted to...
Come on, Liz. Don't make that
kind of disappointed face.
Fine.
Ti!
You better win this.
You know what happens if you don't.
Yes, ma'am!
You can count on me.
I will definitely win that mask!
I mean, I'm the one who'll
be giving her the signal,
so if she doesn't win,
it won't be her fault...
Looks like she prepared her funds.
What will be, will be.
Sold!
Entry number 14, the Mirror Shield,
sold for 15 million gil
to bidder number 413!
Next up, we have entry number 15.
So, Krai, when is your relic coming up?
Is it next? The one after?
Sorry, but it won't be
coming out for a while.
It's a popular item, so I'm
guessing they're dragging it out.
What, it's last?
Tell me about it.
Since my funds are limited,
I can't bid on anything else until
the Reversible Face comes out.
If it came out in the first half,
I could bid on other relics afterward, too!
Next up, we have entry number 16!
Next up, we have entry number 17!
This sword can change its length from
30 centimeters to three meters at will!
I want it! I want it!
Is she urging me? Am I being urged?
"Master, are you sure you
don't want to buy that?"
Is Tino testing me?!
I want it!
I want to participate!
I want to participate in the auction!
But the funds...
But wait.
I've still got an ace up my sleeve.
No, no, hang on.
I really can't do that.
This isn't an emergency situation.
Or is it?
Is this not an emergency?
It is, right?!
Next up, we've got a cloak that
allows you to breathe underwater!
I want it. I want it! I want it!
Damn it, why do all the fun
relics need to come out today?!
If it weren't for the Reversible Face,
I could have bought so many!
Tino's looking at me again.
She's looking at me!
She's testing my love for relics!
Do I even care about the mask anymore?!
Quantity over quality?
I feel like I'm quietly watching someone
else take away the girl I like!
Boots that can make you
levitate one centimeter!
Would you actually use
those after buying them?!
I would!
So please give them to me!
Argh, why aren't I wealthy?!
I want relics! I want relics!
I can't stand it anymore!
I'm not proud of it, but I've got
less self-control than anyone else!
Let's buy them.
Let's give her the sign.
I'm sure Tino will praise me for it, too.
A crystal ball that predicts the
weather with 70 percent accuracy!
I want it!
Hold on. I may have an ace up my sleeve,
but if I were to bid on another
relic now, Sitri would...
probably say nothing and
let me get away with it.
Has the time come?
Krai?
What's up?
This farce ends now.
I will show you how terrifying
I can really be.
Burn this image into your retinas!
This is Thousand Tricks going into
debt with his childhood friends
to go on a relic-buying frenzy!
Next up, we have entry number 44.
An item from our empire's pride and joy,
the Institute for Relic Research!
A metal golem constructed
by a certain magic association!
A golem?
So not a relic?
Si, isn't that...?
Huh?
Akasha?
What is it doing here?
You mean...
If possible, I'd like us to get our hands
on the Akasha golem and the Malice Eaters.
We'll start the bid at 30 million gil!
I've got 30 million.
35 million.
40 million!
Over there, 50 million.
Sitri, what do you want to do?
Nothing. It's fine.
If I bid on that, we won't
be able to get your relic.
It's just that...
creating that took an enormous
amount of my time and money.
But that's not the only
thing that's important.
I don't know how anyone else feels,
but to me, it's like a
memento of my colleagues.
So it has sentimental value?
It's fine. Don't worry about me.
I'm totally fine.
You're such a liar, Sitri.
We've got 300 million gil!
And now, we've got 330 million.
The bid is still climbing higher!
330 million!
380 million!
Krai.
Are you really sure?
If you keep going, we won't
be able to get your relic.
It's fine.
This is how money is meant to be used.
You go, Krai.
It's all basically Sitri's money, anyway.
400 million!
And we've already passed it!
All right, 410 million!
We've got 430 million!
Sitri usually endures things in silence.
440 million!
450 million!
There it is, 470 million!
But look at her face...
480 million!
Can we get 490 million?!
The Akashic Tower probably
stole skills and inventions
from her alchemist colleagues
to build that golem.
Or something like that.
That's why she called it a memento.
500 million!
We're now at 500 million!
500 million?
I could buy so many other relics with that!
That's enough, Krai.
If we keep this up, we won't
be able to buy your relic.
Don't worry about that.
Huh?
Actually, I've been collecting money
to get this golem all along.
Krai...
But Si's budget is 950 million gil.
Let's just hope the others
give up before then.
760 million gil!
830 million gil!
Yes, over there, 950 million gil!
Don't.
Don't. Don't. Don't. Don't!
There it is!
990 million gil!
Over our budget.
Huh?
What?!
Entry number 44.
The silver golem has been sold for
1 billion and 60 million gil!
Oh, boy.
Looks like their limit was 1 billion.
Krai...
That was 110 million over our budget!
It's a serious crime if you can't pay up!
Oh, but Ti placed the bid,
so it's not our problem.
Don't worry.
I've got an ace up my sleeve.
Krai?
Sitri.
With this, we have exactly enough.
So go pay.
Krai...
Thank you so much!
I promise to pay you back!
Yup, yup.
You go, Krai.
Well, if you're going to pay
it back, it goes to Lucia.
Ever seen an older brother
use half of his little sister's
savings for his childhood friend?
Have you?!
We have now received information
about the metal golem's bidder!
Setting a record bid at
1 billion and 60 million gil...
is bidder number 66!
His name is Greg Zangief!
Why is it The Great Greg?
One billion...
How do you feel, Greg?
Master, I'm really sorry.
I didn't actually know
how to bid in an auction.
Greg said he did,
so I asked him to handle it.
Then this happened...
Don't worry about it.
Greg is a veteran hunter.
I'm sure he won't flap his
gums about me and Sitri.
It looks like you've spent a lot of money,
so what are you gonna do about that relic?
It's still due to appear, right?
It's fine.
I got what I wanted, anyway.
Really?
Yeah.
I'm pretty tired, so I'm headed home now.
It looks like Sitri and the others
will have to pick up the golem.
You guys stay here and have a good time.
Master...
I know we're all having a great time!
Ladies and gentlemen, the relic
you've all been waiting for...
is about to take center stage!
I swear, I will definitely give
that all-powerful relic to Ark!
Oh, right!
Let me get straight to the point.
Please go see Lady Éclair right away.
Everything will be made clear.
Is this about that one relic?
I heard she wanted to win the bid for it.
Yeah.
I don't know if she heard my warning or not,
but that thing's a bit dangerous.
Hey!
You're giving us vague information again!
Are you trying to make Ark your gofer?
Yup, yup.
Go yourself!
A dangerous relic?
Yes, in a way.
But you can handle it.
If you go now, I think
you'll make it in time.
I see.
Do I need weapons?
Huh?
Oh. No, you don't.
In fact, I think it's
best if you don't take any.
And what if I'm too late?
Then I'll be sad.
All set.
Lady Éclair will give Ark the relic.
Then I'll buy it off him for
the friends-and-family price.
Why didn't I do this from the start?
Yup, yup.
The problem is whether or not
Ark will accept the gift...
Knowing her, she'd probably throw
a temper tantrum if he didn't.
In the end, he'll have to take it.
I'm going to have to thank him!
I know!
He let you win.
Why do you say that, Father?
I won the bid for the relic.
I won against him!
Do you still not see?
Thousand Tricks has already
left the auction hall.
I also have a report that he had
funds far beyond 200 million...
Win or lose, if he were to take
us on, some ill will would remain.
This is utterly vexing!
We spent 200 million just to learn
how capable Thousand Tricks is.
He took pity on me.
He let me win.
And what did I gain? This creepy thing.
I can't give this to Ark.
How can this be the all-powerful relic?
I'm so... powerless...
Do you desire power?
Sorry?
I've been watching all this time.
Lament. Sorrow.
Wrath. Despair.
You are fit to receive my power, weak one.
I elevate people.
I give hope to those who are weary.
Answer me, Thousand Tricks.
What does this mask do?
That I cannot say.
But if my predictions are right,
that relic is a bit dangerous.
Dangerous... Dangerous...
I see.
So Lady Éclair did that for me...
What a pointless endeavor.
Did she really believe that you'd see any
value in gaining strength from a relic?
Éclair has kept herself shut up
in her room since last evening.
But I'm sure she would come out for you.
Thank you for coming. It's a great help.
It's nothing.
Krai, what were you thinking?
What are you trying to do, pushing
a 10-year-old girl into this kind of state?
Why did you make me come here?
What was that?!
Excuse me!
Benetta, directions!
Left, and then the third right!
Don't patronize me.
Don't look at me like that!
Don't patronize me!
I am...
Lady Éclair!
Could that mask be... the relic?
Don't look at me like that!
I've become strong!
I'll kill anyone who mocks me!
Ark...
Lady Éclair. It's me.
A-Ark...?
Ark, is that you?
What in the world happened here?
I got this...
It's the world's strongest relic,
and I got it for you.
I fought to get this, and yet...
Why?
Why do I...
Do I...
Thank you very much.
It's all right now, Lady Éclair.
Would you take off the
mask and let me have it?
Why, Ark?
Why did you bring that?
Oh. No, you don't.
In fact, I think it's
best if you don't take any.
Everyone, select your spells
and attacks very carefully!
We will remove the mask without
harming a hair on Lady Éclair's head!
On my honor as Ark Brave,
we will succeed!
Yes, sir!
I am strong! I am strong!
Nobody can mock me! Nobody can mock me!
I'm all-powerful!
Man, it really makes you laugh, right?
That creepy mask going
for 200 million gil!
Sorry, but truth be told, I thought
it would sell for even more!
You're too greedy.
200 million for that thing
is more than enough.
You're late, losers!
Since when are any of you in the
position to keep me waiting?
I'll kill you.
What the hell do you want?
It's an important yet simple matter.
Krai's scheme is the reason
your relic yielded such a profit.
Which means he deserves a cut.
What?! You really think
we'd go along with that?!
Huh?
I didn't say it would be for nothing.
I'll sell this to you for 110 million gil.
What is that?
It's an antidote.
You didn't notice anything unusual
when you were drinking without a care?
Here you go!
Like the taste of the beer being a bit off?
Or that you were getting
drunk faster than usual?
Enjoy!
N-Now that you mention it...
M-My stomach does feel funny.
I don't believe this. You poisoned us?!
We're being nice.
Usually, we'd charge 200 million, but we're
letting you keep 90 million for yourselves!
Since you're level 7, Arnold,
you're probably fine.
But what about the others?
Guys!
So what do you say?
This bargain's to die for!
Forgive me, Ark!
What is the meaning of this?
I wanted to show you how
grateful I am and apologize.
From the looks of it, the young lady must
have thrown quite a tantrum.
A tantrum?
Something like that, but you know, Krai,
that wasn't nearly enough to go on.
I'm really sorry about that.
Speaking of, do you have it?
I don't know everything, you know?
Krai! Don't do anything hasty.
This texture!
Yup, this is the Reversible Face!
Just as I thought I had acquired some
real talent, I got subdued again...
I'll need to change my approach.
It spoke! That's so cool!
Thousand Tricks, I was wrong.
I am grateful that you sent Ark to assist—
Sure. Huh?
So gross.
That's so gross.
Strength, agility, stamina,
magic ability, all E-.
Motivation, zero.
Overall rating, 3 points.
Required base parameters to initiate
Overgreed are not present.
Forcibly disengaging.
This isn't a Reversible Face?
Talking relics are rare,
though, so that's still good.
Can I have this?
Yes, you can have it!
It was wrong of me to go after
a relic that you wanted!
Thanks!
Since you're already here,
why don't you have some cake?
We're back!
Krai.
In the end, the relic became his.
All's well that ends well!
It may have not been the mask he sought,
but don't grieve, our Krai Andrey!
Wait a minute...
So that mask worked on Lady Éclair?
That means even that little
rich girl's stronger than...
Yeah, I really do want to retire.
I think I'm gonna puke.
Level 8 Treasure Vault
"Night Palace"
Right.
Thank you!
All right! I'm going to
go settle this thing!
"Thousand Swords"
Luke Sykol
Hunter Level 6
"Immutable"
Ansem Smart
Hunter Level 7
Yes.
"Avatar of Creation"
Lucia Rogier
Hunter Level 6
I suppose we can wait a little longer.
Yes!
We are now in the golden age
of the treasure hunters!
Among the sparkling talent on
display in the capital of Zebrudia,
there was one man who stood
out amongst all others!
His name is Krai Andrey.
This is an epic tale
full of glory and agony,
of how he became renowned
for being the leader
of the strongest party he founded
with his childhood friends,
and also the master of the strongest clan!
A report to the Association?
Yes, the regular status update
about the Grievers' members.
I did prepare something already, but...
Ah, Eliza.
Yes.
Eliza Beck,
"Lost One"
Eliza Beck
Hunter Level 6
the one and only person to join the
Grieving Souls after we formed.
Our seventh member.
She's a thief from the Desert Nobles.
Maybe it's because she's a free spirit,
or because she always has wanderlust...
But we haven't seen her in some time.
Just write in whatever.
I guess we have no choice.